Rockville Journal World War II Letters
Vernon Historical Society
- Inventory
  - Chapman, Buell I, Dec 13, 1943; Fort Knox; KY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chapman, Eleanor, Oct 16, 1944; Middletown; CT; SEE BROWN/MARION POSTCARD; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chapman, William R, Jun 11, 1944; Bedford; PA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chapman, Buell I, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; 12 Rau Street; Son of Mr and Mrs Carl Chapman; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chapman, Harold L, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; 12 Rau Street; Son of Mr and Mrs Carl Chapman; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chapman, Norman B, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chapman, William R, May 02, 1944; Sampson NY; Finished Training,On Leave; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chapman, Norman, Mar 31, 1944; Ft Benning; GA; Finished Paratroop School; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Charter, Edward F, Jun 08, 1948; Lockland AFB,San Antonio; TX; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Charter, Wesley E, Sep 21, 1945; Newport; RI; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Charter, Wesley E, Nov 13, 1945; Brooklyn; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Charter, Wesley E, Aug 24, 1945; Newport; RI; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Charter, Wesley E, Jun 24, 1945; Sampson; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chase, Robert C, undated; Pearl Harbor; HI; Arrived for Assignment; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chatterton, James R, May 18, 1944; Admiralty Islands; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chatterton, Robert G, Feb 20, 1945; Germany; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chatterton, Robert G, Oct 20, 1944; England; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chatterton, James R, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chatterton, James R, Mar 16, 1943; Seymour Johnson,NC; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chatterton, Robert G, Jan 22, 1945; Mrs Ralph Wilcox; Service Update; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chatterton, Arthur, Dec 07, 1945; Mitchell Field; NY; Discharged; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chatterton, James R, Sep 15, 1944; 13 AAF; Southwest Pacific; Description of Military Action; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chatterton, James R, May 04, 1944; South Pacific; Awarded Medal; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chatterton, James R, ..1945; Atlantic City; NJ; On Leave After Flying 44 Missions; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chatterton, James R, Apr 10, 1944; Air Force; South Pacific; Awarded Medal; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chemistruck, Alice, May 09, 1943; Fort Benning; GA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chemistruck, Alice, May 30, 1944; New Guinea; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chemistruck, Alice, May 01, 1945; South Sea Islands; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chemistruck, Alice, Mar 28, 1944; Fort Benning; GA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chemistruck, Alice, Apr 08, 1943; Fort Benning; GA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chemistruck, Alice, undated; New Guinea; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chemistruck, Alice, Dec 13, 1943; Fort Benning; GA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chemistruck, Stephen A, Mar 20, 1944; South Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chemistruck, Stephen A, undated; San Francisco; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chemistruck, Stephen A, Nov 22, 1943; South Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chemistruck, Alice, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chemistruck, Stephen A, Apr 01, 1943; Fort Leonard Wood,MO; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chemistruck, Stephen A, Apr 08, 1943; Fort Leonard Wood,MO; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chemistruck, Alice, Jan 06, 1943; Daytona Beach, FL; City Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chemistruck, Stephen A, Jun 10, 1943; Fort Leonard Wood,MO; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chemistruck, Stephen A, Apr 01, 1943; FortLeonardWood,MO; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chemistruck, Alice, Apr 27, 1945; Dutch East indies; SWAP WACS First Year of Service; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chemistruck, Stephen A, Mar 22, 1945; Philippines; Description of Battle; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chemistruck, Alice, undated; Netherlands; East indies; Wore Gown of parachute Silk to Attend Ball; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chemistruck, Stephen A, Dec 01, 1944; South Pacific; In Anti-Tank Unit; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chemistruck, Alice, Nov 23, 1944; Southwest Pacific; In Military, Mention Article Military Brother; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chemistruck, Stephen A, May 15, 1944; Bouganville; South Pacific; Awarded Medal; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chemistruck, Stephen A, Feb 19, 1945; Philippines; Story About Relations with Civilians; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chemistruck, Stephen A, undated; Philippines; Story About Relations with Civilians; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chemistruck, Stephen A, Nov 23, 1944; Southwest Pacific; Military Service, Sister in Military; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chessey, Joseph J, Oct 19, 1944; Italy; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chifert, Raymond A, Jan 30, 1946; Birmingham; AL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chmielewski, Norbert V, undated; Sampson NY; Finished Training,On Leave; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chorches, Leon J, Dec 09, 1944; South Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chorches, Leon J, undated; Tolland Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chrzanowski, Joseph, Mar 27, 1945; Chanute Field; IL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Chrzanowski, Stanley H, Jan 16, 1945; Germany; Miltary Service; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Ciechowski, Aloysius, Feb 03, 1943; Northwest Africa; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Ciechowski, Aloysius, May 10, 1944; Anzio; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Ciechowski, Aloysius, Feb 26, 1945; APO NY; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Ciechowski, Bernard B, Dec 20, 1944; USS Sable; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Ciechowski, Bernard B, Nov 27, 1943; USS Sable; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Ciechowski, Aloysius, Jun 08, 1943; Algiers; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Ciechowski, Aloysius, Dec 05, 1943; Italy; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Ciechowski, Bernard B, Sep 15, 1945; USS Alaska; Pacific; Battle Description; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Clark, Roy H, Jul 27, 1944; Vernon Honor Roll; Killed in Action,France; Son of Mr and Mrs Ernest E Clark; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Clark, Raymond B, Dec 15, 1943; Sampson NY; Finished Training,On Leave; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Clark, Lincoln R, May 05, 1944; New London; CT; Finished Basic Training Submarine School; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Clark, Raymond B, undated; Norfolk; VA; Trained to Operate Amphibious Craft; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Clark, Roy H., undated; Vernon; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Clough, Warren E, undated; Tolland Honor Roll; in Germany; Son of Mr and Mrs Emery Clough; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Cole, Edwin R, undated; Great Lakes; IL; Graduation from Engineering Course; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Colombaro, Max P, undated; South Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Conlin, Robert H, undated; England; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Connell, Clifton T, undated; Selfridge Field; MI; Reported for Duty; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Connors, Edward J, undated; Fort Custer; MI; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Cor, Abraham E., undated; Miami Beach, FL; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Corbin, Lewis, undated; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Cormier, Tillman, undated; Scott Field; IL; See:Raymond Fahey and Charles Eastwood; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Cosgrove, William J, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Cosgrove, William J, undated; Sioux Falls,SD; City Life; State Pen,Sioux Falls; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Cosgrove, William J, undated; Keesler Field,MS; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Cosgrove, William J, undated; England; War Service; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Cosgrove, William J, undated; Atlantic City; NJ; Back from Europe, Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Cosgrove, William J, undated; 8th Air Force; England; Trainining as Radio Operator and Gunner; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Cosgrove, William J, undated; 8th Air Force; England; Awarded Medal; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Cosgrove, William J, undated; 8th Air Force; England; Awarded Medal; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Cosgrove, William J., undated; Tech Sargeant; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Craczyk, William, undated; Pearl Harbor; HI; Returning Home; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Crandall, Bradford S, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; 53 Spring Street; Son of Mrs Walter Meyer; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Crandall, Howard E, undated; New London; CT; Completed Submarine School; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Cratty, George, undated; Camp Wallace; TX; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Cratty, Robert, undated; France; w/Poem; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Cratty, Robert, undated; Etampes, France; w/Poem; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Cratty, Robert, undated; Camp Hood; TX; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Cratty, Robert, undated; Etampes, France; w/Description of Allied Bombing of Town; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Cratty, Robert, undated; Poem about D-Day, 2 Copies; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Cratty, George, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Wounded; Son of Mr and Mrs Patrick Cratty; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Cratty, Robert, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; France; Son of Mr and Mrs Patrick Cratty; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Cratty, Thomas W, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Europe POW; Son of Mr and Mrs Patrick Cratty; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Cratty, Thomas W, undated; Lake Placid,NY; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Cratty, Thomas W, undated; France; Assigned to 90th Division; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Crawford, John E, undated; 106th Infantry; Germany; Unit Receives Citation,Regimental History; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Crosby, William L, undated; Miami Beach; FL; Reassignment, Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Currier, Alice, undated; England; Red Cross Director; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Curry, Beatrice M, undated; Camp Endicott; RI; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Curry, Beatrice M, undated; Camp Endicott; RI; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Curry, Beatrice M, undated; Camp Endicott,RI; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Curtis, Frederick L, undated; Germany; On Duty in Germany; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A- De)
  - Czarnecki, Bruno S, undated; 5th Army; Italy; Description 81st Mech Cavalry Recon Squad; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Czerwinski, Joseph L, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Czerwinski, Joseph L, undated; Wilmington, DE; City Life; Center Dining Car; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Czerwinski, Joseph L, undated; Wilmington, DE; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Czewinski, Joseph L, undated; Air Transport Command; India; Promotion with Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dailey, Eleanor M, undated; Lincoln; NE; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dailey, Eleanor M, undated; Vaughan Gen Hospital; Hine, IL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dailey, Eleanor M, undated; Amarillo; TX; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dailey, Eleanor M, undated; Lincoln; NE; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dailey, Thomas E, undated; Camp Pendleton; Oceanside, CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dailey, Thomas E, undated; Guam; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dailey, Thomas, undated; Boat Basin,Oceanside,CA; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dailey, Eleanor M, undated; Lincoln,NE; City Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dailey, Eleanor M, undated; Amarillo,TX; Humor; Rio Grande; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dailey, Thomas E, undated; Camp Pendleton,CA; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dailey, Thomas E, undated; Parris Island, SC; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dailey, Thomas E, undated; Dunedin,FL; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dailey, Catherine B, undated; Washington; DC; Discharged Notice; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dalton, Leroy A, undated; Bainbridge; MD; Qualified as Hospital Apprentice; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Darcey, Owen A, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Darcy, John C, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dart, Charles E, undated; Fort Lewis; WA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dart, Charles E, undated; Fort Lewis; WA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dart, Charles E, undated; Camp Gruber; OK; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dart, Charles E, undated; Fort Lewis; WA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dart, Charles E, undated; Grant; IL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dart, Ralph, undated; Camp Blonding; FL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dart, Ralph, undated; New Address; PC-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dart, Charles E, undated; Camp Grant,IL; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dart, Charles E, undated; Camp Gruber,OK; City Life; US Veterans' Hospital,Muskogee,OK; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Davies, Erwin R, undated; Camp Stewart,GA; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Davies, Erwin R, undated; Fort Jackson, SC; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Davies, Edwin R, undated; Paris,France; City Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Davies, Alfred C, undated; 5th Army; Italy; Promoted; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Davies, Alfred C, undated; 5th Army; Italy; Promoted; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Davis, Frederick, undated; Europe; w/Photos; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Davis, Frederick, undated; France; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Davis, Frederick, undated; Germany; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Davis, Frederick, undated; France; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Davis, Harold G, undated; Chanute Field; IL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Davis, Harold G, undated; Cuyohoga Fall; OH; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Davis, Harold G, undated; Kiesler Field; MS; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Davis, Merritt T, undated; New York City; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Davis, Roy P, undated; Yuma; AZ; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Davis, Frederick, undated; New Address, Mae Varish; PC-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Davis, George, undated; New Address; PC-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Davis, Harold G, undated; Rantoul,IL; Air Force; Chanute Field,IL; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Davis, Harold G, undated; Daniel Field,GA; Augusta; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Davis, Harold G, undated; Rantoul,IL; Humor; Canute Field; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Davis, Frederick, undated; Holland; Scenery; Valkenburg; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Davis, Harold G, undated; Cuyahoga Falls,OH; War Bonds; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Davis, Roy P, undated; Chanute Field,IL; Finished Electronics Instruction; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Davis, George J, undated; New Delhi; India; Received Award; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Davis, Edwin, undated; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dawbow, Wesley, undated; San Fransisco,CA; Scenery; Golden Gate Bridge; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dawgewicz, Leonard, undated; Farmingdale,NY; War Bonds; See also:Dowgiewcz, Leonard; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dawhan, W., undated; San Fransisco,CA; City Life; Y.M.C.A.; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dawkins, John C, undated; Ithica NY; Completed Training; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dawkins, Joan, undated; Camp Butner; NC; Radio Training; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dawkins, Joan, undated; Fort Oglethorpe; GA; Will Attend Special School; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dawkins, Thomas H, undated; Guam; Returning Home, Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dawson, James, undated; Mentioned in Letter From J Neiman; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dawson, James, undated; New York City; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dawson, James, undated; Charleston, NC; Camp Life; Citadel; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - DeCarli, Joseph, undated; Naha; Okinawa; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - DeCarli, Joseph, undated; Camp Pickett,VA; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - DeCarli, Joseph, undated; Camp Pickett, VA; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - DeCarli, Joseph, undated; Camp Pickett,VA; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - DeCarli, Hodie, undated; Mrs DeCarli; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - DeCarli, Joseph, undated; Mrs DeCarli; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deschaine, Wilfred, undated; Vernon; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deere, Cyril Thomas, undated; Naval Hospital; San Francisco; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deere, Cyril Thomas, undated; Camp Lee; VA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deere, Cedric, undated; New Address, Mrs Brown; PC-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - DeHulla, Donald R, undated; Solomon's Branch; MD; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - DeHulla, Donald R, undated; Bainbridge; MD; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - DeHulla, Donald R, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - DeHullz, Donald R, undated; Sampson,NY; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - DelBene, Eugene J., undated; New Guinea; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - DelBene, Eugene J., undated; South Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - DelBene, Eugene J., undated; Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - DelBene, Howard J, undated; South Pacific; Co-signed Letter Under Farr/Larry; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - DelBene, Eugene J., undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Killed in Action,Luzon; Son of Mr and Mrs Louis DelBene; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - DelBene, Francis J, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - DelBene, Howard J, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - DelBene, Eugene J., undated; Vernon; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Denley, Donald F, undated; Sasebo; Japan; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Denley, Donald F, undated; Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Denley, Donald F, undated; Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Denley, Donald F, undated; Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Denley, Donald F, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Denley, Donald F, undated; Camp Le Jeune,NC; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Denson, Gordon A, undated; APO NY; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Denson, Gordon A, undated; England; Clipping Sent by Edwin C McLaughlin; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Denson, Gordon A, undated; Napier Field; AL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Denson, Gordon A, undated; New Address, Alice Denson; PC-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Denson, Gordon A, undated; New Address, Alice Denson; PC-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Denson, Gordon A, undated; New Address; PC-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Denson, Gordon A, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Denson, Gordon A, undated; Greenville,MS; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Denson, Gordon A, undated; Columbia,SC; City Life; Post Office; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Denson, Gordon A, undated; Atlantic City,NJ; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Denson, Gordon A, undated; Dale Mabry Field,FL; Tallahassee,FL; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Denson, Gordan A, undated; 8th Air Force; England; Description of Air Battle; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Denson, Gordan A, undated; 8th Air Force; England; Military Record, Battle Descriptions; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Denson, Gordan A, undated; 8th Air Force; England; Military Record; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Denson, Gordan A, undated; England; Promotion; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Denson, Gordan A, undated; Napier Field; AL; Received Pilot's Wings; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Denson, Gordan A, undated; 8th Air Force; On List of 8th AF after VE Day; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - DePellegrini, Jeanne M, undated; San Francisco; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deptula, John M, undated; Atlantic City; NJ; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deptula, John M, undated; Friend; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deptula, John M, undated; South Pacific; On Furlough; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deschaine, Wilfred, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Killed in Action,Germany; Son of Mr and Mrs Paul Deschaine; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deslauries, Joseph, undated; Fort Bliss; TX; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deslauries, Joseph, undated; Fort Bliss; TX; w/Photo; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deslauries, Joseph, undated; New Delhi; India; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deslauries, Joseph, undated; Camp Gruber; OK; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deslauries, Joseph, undated; India; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deslauries, Joseph, undated; APO NY; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deslauries, Joseph, undated; APO NY; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deslauries, Joseph, undated; APO NY; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deslauries, Joseph, undated; New Delhi; India; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deslauries, Joseph, undated; India; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deslauries, Joseph, undated; Fort Bliss; TX; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deslauries, Joseph, undated; Camp Haan; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)